<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
      <title>danielm's blog</title>
      <link>https://danielm.pw</link>
      <description>programming, philosophy, blog, stoicism</description>
      <atom:link href="https://danielm.pw/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
      <image>
        <title>daniel's blog</title>
        <link>https://danielm.pw</link>
      </image>
      <language>en-us</language>
      <copyright>Creative Commons BY-NC-SA 4.0</copyright>
      <item>
<title>uWHO uAM uI</title>
<description>&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone, my names are Matongo Mulindi but to most people that know me I go by the name of Daniel.&lt;br /&gt;
I’ve never written a blog before, but after what has seemingly been a quasi-quarter life crisis or just an inquisitive youth trying to navigate the chaos that is the millennial age (I’m yet to figure out which of the two it is), I’ve decided to give it a try!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I suppose what has drawn me to this, is the beauty of simultaneously creating something that can be your own whilst availing it to millions of people. To add to that is the subtle beauty of the internet in it’s everlasting and somewhat indestructible nature, to have your mind and thoughts etched into the annals of time, a record that can either be made for positive or negative impact.&lt;br /&gt;
What we record and put out there helps shape the world for us and future generations, this power should be embraced and not hidden away.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Knowledge is power. Power to do evil…or power to do good. Power itself is not evil. So knowledge itself is not evil.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;― Veronica Roth, &lt;a href="https://www.goodreads.com/work/quotes/15524549"&gt;Allegiant&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having been an observant side-liner, I’ve come to realize that I needed a place of expression, a place to tell a story or share my pseudo satirical views of the current status quo.&lt;br /&gt;
So here it is welcome to my blog, my little slice of the internet to express my love for the simple things, to air my voice on all things political, business, and human. A place to share my thoughts with you and hopefully to inspire more people to, no matter who they are, do the same at some level.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I want to take all that I’ve discovered, learned and experienced and share it with the world, with you and in sharing, to grow, discover, learn and experience more things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To be candid, I’m not sure what this blog will become but I’m a firm believer of consistency and it’s rewarding and though life is a fickle mistress (it seems the harder we push against it, the harder it pushes back), so I’m not going to make any grand promises, but what I will promise is to provide my honest, down-to-earth views and opinions and to just be me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With this in mind, I have to give you some pre-warning, I’ve never been much of a poet by any means though I have dabbled and made a few publications to various websites in a much different time so I’ll stick to what I feel comfortable with.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Before I started to write this post, I did a quick google search on what my first post should be about. It gave me a list of what should and shouldn’t be included and I think I’ve covered most of them.&lt;br /&gt;
However, one of the points that resonated with me most, was to encourage you guys to get involved. That could be through asking me questions and suggesting topics for me to cover but also and most importantly, to challenge me. We learn faster and build off our differing opinions, so don’t hold back!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So there you go, a very small snippet of who I am and what to expect! Hopefully, you want to see and learn more about who I am and what I’m doing… If so, read on and enjoy the journey with me.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
<link>https://danielm.pw/posts/WHO_AM_I/</link>
<pubDate>Mon, 10 Aug 2020 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
<guid>https://danielm.pw/posts/WHO_AM_I/</guid>
</item>


    </channel>
</rss>
